#source: https://www.triviaquestionss.com/fun-trivia-questions/ & https://www.quizbreaker.com/trivia-questions
quiz = {
    1 : {
        "question" : "What is the first name of the spouse of Barack Obama?",
        "answer" : "Michelle"
    },
    2 : {
        "question" : "How many teeth are in the adult mouth?",
        "answer" : "32"
    },
    3 : {
        "question" : "How many days are in a fortnight?",
        "answer" : "14"
    },
    4 : {
        "question" : "Which European country consumes the most chocolate per capita?",
        "answer" : "Switzerland"
     },
    5 : {
        "question" : "What geometric shape is generally used for stop signs?",
        "answer" : "Octagon"
    },
    6 : {
        "question" : "Which animal can be seen on the Porsche logo?",
        "answer" : "Horse"
    },
    7 : {
        "question" : "What is the most consumed manufactured drink in the world?",
        "answer" : "Tea"
    },
    8 : {
        "question" : "Which Asian country invented ice cream?",
        "answer" : "China"
    },
    9 : {
        "question" : "Havana is the capital of which North American country?",
        "answer" : "Cuba"
    },
    10 : {
        "question" : "How many legs does a spider have?",
        "answer" : "8"
    }

}